All right, we uh obviously had three
picks today. Uh Logan Jones being the
first one. Uh good opportunity to add
another center. Obviously, that's a been
a tough position for us um since I've
been here really. Um, so we had
opportunity to bring Logan in and um,
high character guy, really smart, uh,
fits our scheme in terms of being able
to run mid zone, wide zone, u, strong,
explosive, has great range, reach and
cut off.
Really liked his tape, so it was a good
addition there. Sam Roush, another
really good addition at the tight end
spot. uh for a team that runs a lot of
12 and 13 personnel. I think we're top
five in both of those personnel groups,
that was important for us to add a Y to
the group. Um so we'll have a really
strong room there. I feel great about
that. And Zavon, um another versatile
player who brings a high level of speed,
explosive speed. Um it jumps off the
tape. Another one that as a group we
watched it over and over and over again.
It was uh we think he has some special
stuff to u really make an impact with
the new kickoff that we have going on in
the NFL. Um putting us in really good
position to uh and field position and
then obviously punt returner as well. Um
can take snaps at running back. Has
really good vision and and explosion and
feel and then obviously can take the top
off as a receiver as well. So we can do
a lot with him. Um, and obviously when
you pair that up with with Ben and
press, um, exciting things can happen.
So, I'll open up from there.
>> What's your vision at center in terms of
wanting experience in front of Caleb,
but then obviously using a premium pick
on a guy in Logan that would seem to
have a an opening to to compete for a
prominent role pretty quickly.
>> Yeah, it's um it's a vital part of our
offense. Uh, and it is it's not easy to
do. Um, so when you come from um, a
school like Iowa, you're taught the
right way. Um, so you understand the
communication aspect of it. You're the
glue. You're the the the circuit board
of that offensive line and and you help
the run game. Um, he's been doing that
for a while now. U, we felt really
comfortable with with his intelligence
and experience to come in and and
compete. Um, and you know, we feel
really good about Garrett being the
starting center. Obviously, we're going
to always compete there. Um, but if
something were to happen, we feel really
good to we're not gonna have a huge letd
down um for him going in the game and
and operating at a high level.
>> Ryan, it seemed like defensive line may
have been a need coming into this draft.
Was it a situation where you guys just
didn't view it the same way as quite the
as big a need or the board just didn't
go that rout?
>> Yeah, the board uh the class um a little
bit this is you know a little life at
the back of the round. um it's different
u but it's it's really how the board you
know shook out
you know when we made that turn into two
had a good sense through um our research
that that was going to kind of be a hot
spot at the very top of two
wasn't really possible to get up that
high without giving up a ton and um
at the end of the day we just follow the
board
>> on a follow up to Herb's question so you
don't get an offensive tackle
anything on the defensive line. So, what
what's your hope or what's your plan at
those spots right now?
>> Yeah. So, the at the defensive line
position, you know, books coming along.
We have Dio, Sweat,
um Shamar, feel good about those guys.
Obviously, we have one more day, so we
continue to add, but like with that that
group is and what they've been coming
and we feel like there's some
developmental upside. Like I said
yesterday, I think year two in the
system, um we'll be able to take the
next step O line wise, we have, you
know, open competition at tackle. Um
guys that have played a lot of football
and we feel confident that those guys
will compete and the best guy will win
at that left tackle position and then
obviously we feel really good about what
Azie did before he got injured and we
like where he's at in his recovery. So
again, we got another day to continue to
add um multiple ways to add throughout
training camp and the spring training
camp and in the season. So um again, we
follow the board. It's it's hard to
if
to go into a draft and and just start
picking at your needs and hopping around
the board and letting all the good guys,
you know, go by just because of of that,
it it doesn't that doesn't play out very
well in the long haul. So, um, we stuck
to the board. Um, every class is going
to be different and like I said, when
you're at the back of the round, it's
it's a little bit different than being
at the, you know, top five, top 10
picks, and I'll trade that any day.
>> This is the second year that you used to
premier pick on a tight end. Do you have
to have a conversation with KT about,
hey, this is I mean, is the plan the
plan is for all three of them to start
the season?
>> Yep. Yeah, we do a good job between Ben
and I. we communicate uh really well
just to give those guys a heads up and
and let them know what the role in the
situation is. Um
you know nothing changes for Cole. Um
our feelings for Cole doesn't change um
again we're top five and 12 and 13
personnel. Um if something were to
happen um injury-wise to Cole or Coulson
all a sudden you're changing a lot of
stuff you know a lot of game plan stuff
that is kind of your bread and butter.
So, uh, we feel good about that room and
and the guys that are in there
>> right with that with the center.
>> Mhm.
>> It strikes me that this a good sort of
tension to have between bringing in a
young player and having a veteran have
to compete for the job. Is that that's
the plan obviously, right?
>> Yeah. I mean, Cole's Cole's locked in. I
mean, even contractwise, he's locked in.
So, um, we're always going to compete.
You know, it's not like you just show up
and your spot's your spot. But we feel
really good about Cole's position on
this team, his role, his leadership.
Like, it's not just whatever spot he is
on tight end dep chart, but his
leadership and what he means to this
team is we view him highly. So, that
doesn't change much at all. But, yeah,
you always want to add competition that
brings out the best of everybody.
>> With Tennessee coming up for 60, were
you getting multiple calls with that
pick? Was there any 57?
>> Oh, man. Yeah, this calls are all over
the place this year. Um this is an
interesting draft in general, but um
yeah, just some different opportunities
looking at your board where can you get
more swings and um we felt like that
worked out well, put us in position
where we still got the guys that we
liked and and then we add a little bit
more for tomorrow.
>> You have a pretty significant gap
between the fourth round and the
seventh. Do you feel like you are you
going in at least hoping that you can
recoup some of that or do you think
you'll be able to walk away with what
you want with the four picks between,
you know, the four rounds?
>> Yeah. So, I think we got a five now. Uh
yeah, so we got four, five, and two
sevens. Yeah. So, we feel pretty good
about that. Um we'll see if there's any
opportunities kind of move around, but
um based on where the board is, we feel
like we got a good shot at some good
players. With Rous,
>> how much does you mentioned 12 and 13
personnel having Ben and his vision,
does that make you feel how how much did
that like help make you feel
comfortable? Because obviously if you
have Coulson, you have Cole, like
there's always so many snaps for those
guys stay healthy.
>> How does Ben allow you to feel
comfortable using that high of a pick on
a guy like that?
>> Yeah, just the plan. Um the plan in
terms of what's important to us and how
we want to operate. Um, anytime you have
clarity like that, it's it's again it
makes the draft process and player
acquisition uh a lot easier. You're not
second guessing how guys are going to
get used. You can see the plan, the
vision, and the clearer that is, the
clearer it is to to pick those guys up.
So,
>> good.
>> Thomas, pick you and uh Francis St. Paul
both very quickly brought up Ben as a
factor in his
>> development. How does your trust in Ben
play into your drafting where if he says
he can do something with a guy or he can
get a guy to fit a certain role that he
needs
>> that that clarity doesn't seem like it
maybe has been here in the years past.
>> Well, when you have that level of
creativity and you can put guys in
position to um really highlight their
specific trait to, you know, create an
advantage. uh you welcome that all the
time. So yeah, his ability to do that
again, it reminds me of where I came
from. Um he has a vision. I he's one you
look next to he's like sketching out
plays and things like that. So um yeah,
when when you go through that and and he
can see it and there's a vision for it,
um you have confidence. Obviously, you
know, the players got to do their part
and there's development things like
that. It's not overnight, but anytime
there's clarity on how we're going to
use players and and and not only just
there, but also High Tower with, you
know, the return game. Um, again, all of
these things can create an advantage and
put us in a good spot.
>> How do you view the with Savian coming
in? I mean, in big picture with the
number three receiver, how do you feel
like he fits in that mix with Khalif and
with Jade?
>> Yeah, so this is a this is a tough
system. So, it's going to be a challenge
for him to to break through u with Khif,
but again, we're going to open that
competition up um for all of these guys
coming in.
I think, you know, you feel really good
about the return um ability that he has.
And then, you know, he'll be in with the
rest of the guys to learn the offense.
And how does he do that? How fast does
that come along? Um you all have talked
to our receivers. It's a challenging
system. Um, so maybe that role starts
small and it grows over time, but you
know, I don't want to put a cap on it.
If he comes in and downloads fast and is
up and running, then then we'll see what
happens.
>> When you look at that, when you were
watching him on tape, are there specific
moments that that you can reflect on and
say, "Hey, that that
>> fun fun tape."
When you get that level of speed,
there's a couple things. I talked about
it with Dylan, too. There's acceleration
like it's that 0 to 60 where you can
just like feel it. Um when he throttles
down I mean he can take off um and get
up to high speeds quick. Uh his ability
to decelerate is impressive as well. Um
and then when you are 190 195
there's a level of breaking tackles
um and kind of getting through some of
that trash. I mean, just, you know, if
you go through his tape and and you cut
down into the running back stuff, um,
for his entire college career, his
ability to run in between the tackles is
really good, too. So, there's a natural
feel, vision, and just overall instincts
u that makes him unique. And he's one of
those I've watched the tape multiple
times, and you you're talent guys that
come in the room and watch this and
coaches get excited, special teams
coaches get excited, everybody's excited
about it. So, uh, unique talent and
excited to see him operate and and learn
and develop while he's here. Did you
know that he was consistent relative to
Walter?
>> No.